<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FindNGO</string>
    <string name="search_for_ngo">Search for NGO</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="layout">layout</string>
    <string name="scrollview">scrollview</string>
    <string name="ngo_categories">NGO Categories</string>

    <string name="about"><b>About Us</b>\n\nWelcome to our <b>NGO Finder</b> app, your one-stop destination for discovering and connecting with non-governmental organizations (NGOs) across India. Our mission is to empower users like you to make informed decisions when it comes to supporting and contributing to the noble causes championed by NGOs.\n\nAt <b>NGO Finder</b>, we understand the importance of transparency and accountability in the NGO sector. That\'s why we provide a comprehensive database of NGOs registered with the Government of India, sourced directly from the NGO Darpan portal (https://ngodarpan.gov.in/). With thousands of NGOs listed on our platform, you can easily explore and discover organizations working in various sectors and regions across the country.\n\nOur app serves both users and developers alike:\n\n<b>For Users:</b>\n\n<b>Discover NGOs:</b> Easily search and explore NGOs based on location, sector, or keyword to find organizations aligned with your interests and values.\n\n<b>Detailed NGO Profiles:</b> Access detailed profiles of NGOs, including their mission, activities, contact information, and registration details.\n\n<b>Verified Information</b>: Rest assured that all NGO data available on our platform is sourced from the official NGO Darpan portal, ensuring authenticity and reliability.\n\n<b>Contact NGOs :</b> Connect directly with NGOs to inquire about their programs, volunteering opportunities, or donation needs before making any contributions.\n\n<b>Stay Informed :</b> Stay updated with the latest news, events, and campaigns from NGOs working on causes you care about.\n\n<b>For Developers:</b>\n\n<b>Upload NGO Data:</b> Developers and NGOs can contribute to our platform by uploading their organization\'s information, ensuring that their work reaches a wider audience.\n\n<b>Collaborate and Innovate:</b> We welcome collaboration with developers to enhance our app\'s features, improve data accuracy, and provide a seamless user experience for our community.\n\nWe believe in the power of technology to drive positive social change. By leveraging the reach of digital platforms, we aim to amplify the impact of NGOs and facilitate meaningful engagement between NGOs, donors, volunteers, and supporters.\n\nJoin us on this journey to create a more inclusive and compassionate society. Together, we can make a difference, one NGO at a time.\n\nThank you for choosing <b>NGO Finder</b>. Let\'s work together to build a better world for all.</string>

</resources>